allgroup.ca 2016-11-12

# Privacy Policy - All Group Financial ServicesAll Group Financial Services

At the time you begin a relationship with us and during the course of our relationship, we may collect information about you. We obtain most of our information about you directly from you. The information we ask for depends on which product or service you want.

Our Privacy Policy informs you of the policies and practices we have in place relating to the management of personal information at All Group Financial Services. The word “information” means personal, financial and other details about you that you provide to us and we obtain from others outside our organization, including through the products and services you use. This policy applies to personal customers, including individuals carrying on business alone or in partnership with other individuals and signing officers of our business customers. It consists of five key principles:

  1. **Identifying Purposes and Obtaining Your Consent**  

> We identify the purposes for collecting personal information at or before the time it is collected.
> 
> We obtain your consent before collecting, using or disclosing personal information, except where permitted or required by law.

  2. **Limiting the Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Information**  

> We limit the personal information we collect to what is necessary for the purposes we have identified. We collect information only by fair and lawful means.
> 
> We do not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent, or where permitted or required by law. We retain personal information only as long as necessary for these purposes.

  3. **Keeping Your Information Accurate and Providing Access to Your Information**  

> We take care to keep personal information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used.
> 
> Upon request, we provide you with access to your personal information. You can ask how your information is used or disclosed, can ensure it is accurate and complete, and can update it if necessary.

  4. **Protecting Your Information**  

> We safeguard the privacy of personal information through security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information.

  5. **Addressing Your Concerns**  

> We are responsible for personal information under our control. There are designated individuals within All Group Financial Services who are accountable for compliance with these privacy principles.
> 
> We make available to you, information about our policies and practices related to managing your personal information.
> 
> We address your concerns. We have steps you can follow if you have questions or concerns about your privacy.
